{
    "name": ".\\Italian\\Italian8.json",
    "vocab": [
        {
            "alternates": [
                "il tappeto e' rosso"
            ],
            "answer": "Il tappeto e' rosso.",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1517433962.617199,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"The rug is red.\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "beautiful",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1517433954.9451485,
            "question": "Given the definition \"bello\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "nuova",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1517433957.6145792,
            "question": "new (singular, feminine)",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "the beds are small"
            ],
            "answer": "The beds are small.",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1517433967.80967,
            "question": "Given the definition \"I letti sono piccoli.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "i cuscini sono gialli"
            ],
            "answer": "I cuscini sono gialli.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517433898.7033079,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"The pillows are yellow.\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "old",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517433921.570783,
            "question": "Given the definition \"vecchio\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "the pillows are yellow"
            ],
            "answer": "The pillows are yellow.",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1517433973.5899026,
            "question": "Given the definition \"I cuscini sono gialli.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "the table is green"
            ],
            "answer": "The table is green.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517433904.4380484,
            "question": "Il tavolo e' verde.",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "brutto",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1517434272.041717,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"ugly\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "i piatti sono blu"
            ],
            "answer": "I piatti sono blu.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517434139.3800075,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"The dishes are blue.\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "la cucina e' grande"
            ],
            "answer": "La cucina e' grande.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517433981.0769799,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"The kitchen is big.\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "i letti sono piccoli"
            ],
            "answer": "I letti sono piccoli.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517434130.4260824,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"The beds are small.\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "le pentole sono nere"
            ],
            "answer": "Le pentole sono nere.",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1517434277.1785731,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"The pans are black.\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "le camare nuove"
            ],
            "answer": "le camere nuove",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1517434262.4155748,
            "question": "Given the definition \"the new bedrooms\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "le camera da letto sono belle",
                "le camere da letto sono belle"
            ],
            "answer": "Le camera da letto sono belle.",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1517434251.3259053,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"The bedrooms are beautiful.\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "la casa e' vecchia"
            ],
            "answer": "Le casa e' vecchia.",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1517434269.7703898,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"The house is old.\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "the new beds",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517434286.932145,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"i letti nuovi\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "the couch is new"
            ],
            "answer": "The couch is new",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517434354.4466355,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Il divano e' nuovo.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "the pans are black"
            ],
            "answer": "The pans are black.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517434318.7454262,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Le pentole sono nere.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "the new bedrooms",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1517434365.2836456,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"le camere nuove\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "nuovi",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517434312.0035338,
            "question": "new (plural, masculine)",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "the rug is red"
            ],
            "answer": "The rug is red.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517434344.6642098,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Il tappeto e' rosso.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "the pillows are blue"
            ],
            "answer": "The pillows are blue.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517434306.580788,
            "question": "I cuscini sono blu.",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "the house is small"
            ],
            "answer": "The house is small.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517434349.5678542,
            "question": "La casa e' piccola.",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "il divano nuovo",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517434399.7793813,
            "question": "Given the definition \"the new couch\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "ugly",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517434412.817999,
            "question": "Given the definition \"brutto\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "il divano e' nuovo"
            ],
            "answer": "Il divano e' nuovo.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517434374.5561993,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"The couch is new\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "the bathroom is ugly"
            ],
            "answer": "The bathroom is ugly.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517434410.9161172,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Il bagno e' brutto.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "the couch is new"
            ],
            "answer": "The couch is new.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517434417.252752,
            "question": "Il divano e' nuovo.",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "le sedie sono marroni"
            ],
            "answer": "Le sedie sono marroni.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517434425.202522,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"The chairs are brown.\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "the table is green"
            ],
            "answer": "The table is green.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517434405.2366757,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Il tavolo e' verde.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "big",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517434418.899864,
            "question": "Given the definition \"grande\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "il tavolo e' verde"
            ],
            "answer": "Il tavolo e' verde.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517434439.1060247,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"The table is green.\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "the kitchen is large"
            ],
            "answer": "The kitchen is big.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517434496.152264,
            "question": "Given the definition \"La cucina e' grande.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "small",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517434427.289373,
            "question": "Given the definition \"piccola\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "the big kitchen",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517434499.670922,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"la cucina grande\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "the chairs are brown"
            ],
            "answer": "The chairs are brown.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517434489.3715718,
            "question": "Le sedie sono marroni.",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "the bathroom is ugly"
            ],
            "answer": "The bathroom is ugly.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517434465.8913221,
            "question": "Il bagno e' brutto.",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "piccola",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517434468.2005384,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"small\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "nuova"
            ],
            "answer": "nuovo",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517434482.686299,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"new\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "the big bathroom",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517434531.2992265,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"il bagno grande\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "new",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517434527.4759731,
            "question": "Given the definition \"nuovo\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "nuovo",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517434524.5860164,
            "question": "new (singular, masculine)",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "the new house",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517434518.333035,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"la casa nuova\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "la casa nuova",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517434505.29609,
            "question": "Given the definition \"the new house\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "the plates are blue"
            ],
            "answer": "The dishes are blue.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517434514.4739535,
            "question": "Given the definition \"I piatti sono blu.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "bella"
            ],
            "answer": "bello",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517434521.952137,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"beautiful\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "the washing machine is white"
            ],
            "answer": "The washing machine is white.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517434538.0321202,
            "question": "La lavatrice e' bianca.",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "il bagno e' brutto"
            ],
            "answer": "Il bagno e' brutto.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517434612.4847362,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"The bathroom is ugly.\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "the house is old"
            ],
            "answer": "The house is old.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517434557.262335,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Le casa e' vecchia.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "the washing machine is white"
            ],
            "answer": "The washing machine is white.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517434607.3970823,
            "question": "Given the definition \"La lavatrice e' bianca.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "i letti nuovi",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517434547.8270764,
            "question": "Given the definition \"the new beds\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "il bagno grande",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517434573.2240732,
            "question": "Given the definition \"the big bathroom\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "la lavatrice e' bianca"
            ],
            "answer": "La lavatrice e' bianca.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517434600.31634,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"The washing machine is white.\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "nuove",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517434560.4839127,
            "question": "new (plural, feminine)",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "vecchio",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517434550.9229934,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"old\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "the chairs are brown"
            ],
            "answer": "The chairs are brown.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517434639.3137176,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Le sedie sono marroni.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "grande",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517434634.3402138,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"big\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "the kitchen is large"
            ],
            "answer": "The kitchen is large.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517434647.5150006,
            "question": "La cucina e' grande.",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "the new couch",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517434642.2934108,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"il divano nuovo\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "la cucina grande",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517434619.97299,
            "question": "Given the definition \"the big kitchen\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "The bedrooms are beautiful"
            ],
            "answer": "The bedrooms are beautiful.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517434632.4393408,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Le camera da letto sono belle.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        }
    ]
}